(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-15T12:45:39.926020",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
いくつかの夢という花が
Flowers of countless dreams...
この惑星には咲いていたんだ
were blooming on this planet.
「自分もきっと」って憧れては
"I'm sure I can, too," admiring it,
思いきり葉を広げたんだ
I spread my leaves to my heart's content.
そう不安なときも いつも支えてくれていたんだ
Even during uneasy times, my roots...
根っこ
have always supported me.
だからきっともっと 大きくなれる！
That's why I'm sure I can grow even bigger!
想いは真っ直ぐ、伸びてゆけ
Feelings, shoot straight and grow...
あの空に届くように
so they reach that sky!
もう怖いものなんてない
With no more fear left,
めいっぱい咲かせるよ
I'll make them bloom in full!
自分という名の大きな花
A grand flower by the name of myself,
満開の桃の花
full-bloomed peach blossoms.
あーみんな！
Ah, everyone!
あー、いいね。みんな誰も見てなかった！
Ah, good. No one was looking!
いいね。もう１回 最初から始めよう！
Good, let's start over from the very beginning!
いぇい！
Yay!
あ、今度こそねねが…
Ah, this time for sure, Nene...
誰にいるか、わかりますかー？
Do you know who's here? Can you tell?
わあ！見える見える！
Yay! You can see me!
いくつかの夢という花が
Flowers of countless dreams...
この惑星には咲いていたんだ
were blooming on this planet.
「自分もきっと」って憧れては
"I'm sure I can, too," admiring it,
思いきり葉を広げたんだ
I spread my leaves to my heart's content.
そう不安なときも いつも支えてくれていたんだ
Even during uneasy times, my roots...
根っこ
have always supported me.
だからきっともっと 大きくなれる！
That's why I'm sure I can grow even bigger!
想いは真っ直ぐ、伸びてゆけ
Feelings, shoot straight and grow...
あの空に届くように
so they reach that sky!
もう怖いものなんてない
With no more fear left,
めいっぱい咲かせるよ
I'll make them bloom in full!
自分という名の大きな花
A grand flower by the name of myself,
満開の桃の花
full-bloomed peach blossoms.
そう不安なときも
Even during uneasy times,
いつも支えてくれているねこ
you've always supported and given me strength.
だからきっともっと大きくなれる
That's why I'm sure I can grow even bigger,
想いはまっすぐ伸びてゆけ
and my feelings will keep stretching...
あの空に届くように
so they reach that sky!
君が持ってきた漫画
The manga you brought along
くれた知らない名前のお花
and the flower with an unknown name you gave me...
今日はまだ来ないかな?
Are you not coming today?
初めての感情知ってしまった
I've come to know emotions for the very first time.
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって
Tracing the painting decorated by the window,
ひとりで宇宙を旅して
traveling through space all by myself,
みんな、おうちにプレゼントが届いてる人は開けてください！おーりゃ！
Everyone, if you received a present at home, please open it! Here we go!
暗いね、何が入ってるかというとね、目のサイリウムほら！おーりゃ、くれ！
It's dark! As for what's inside... look at the eye cyalumes! Hey, give it here!
おらおらおらおらみんな届けてうおおお！
Take this, everyone, deliver it, whoa!
すごい量が出るんだから！
Because a huge amount comes out!
下のひともほら、真下の人も食らえ、直撃でうおおお！
People below too, look, people right underneath, eat this, direct hit, whoa!
思い出太陽の光浴びて、鮮やかに輝くよ、空を全部…
Bathed in the light of the sun of memories, shining brilliantly, lighting up the whole sky...
メインいっぱいこの両手広げてさあ！
With both hands spread wide, come on!
ありがとうみんな！開けてくれたかな？Twitterとかよかったら載せて見せてね！
Thank you everyone! Did you open it? If you'd like, post it on Twitter and show me!
ああもうない！
Ah, there's no more!
みんながいればなんでもできるよ！思いばまっすぐ伸びてゆけ、あの空に届くように！
If everyone's here, I can do anything! May my thoughts stretch straight ahead, reaching that sky!
ものばいものなんてないメインいっぱい咲かせるよ！みんなでさかそうたくさんの花、満開のモノの花！
Making flowers bloom with all my might! Let's make lots of flowers bloom together, flowers in full bloom!
みんな見て！ねねは何に一体乗ってるんだ？これはなんだなんだ？わあ、地面が、地面が狂う！
Everyone look! What on earth am I riding on? What is this? Whoa, the ground, the ground is going crazy!
君が持ってきた漫画
The manga you brought along
くれた知らない名前のお花
and the flower with an unknown name you gave me...
今日はまだ来ないかな?
Are you not coming today?
初めての感情知ってしまった
I've come to know emotions for the first time.
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって
Tracing the painting decorated by the window,
ひとりで宇宙を旅して
traveling through space all by myself,
それだけでいいはずだったのに
That should have been enough, but...
君の手を握ってしまったら
Once I grabbed your hand,
孤独を知らないこの街には
to this city that knows no loneliness,
もう二度と帰ってくることは
I probably won't ever be able
できないのだろう
to return again.
君が手を差し伸べた光で影が生まれる
Shadows are born from the light where you reached out your hand.
歌って聞かせて この話の続き
Sing and let me hear the rest of this story,
連れて行って 見たことない星まで
take me away to a star I've never seen before.
君が持ってきた漫画
The manga you brought me,
くれた 知らない名前のお花
and the flower with an unknown name you gave me.
今日はまだ来ないかな?
Will you still not come today?
初めての感情 知ってしまった
I've come to know feelings for the very first time.
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって ひとり宇宙を旅をして
Tracing the painting on the window, traveling the universe alone,
それだけでいいはずだったのに
when that alone should have been enough,
君の手を握ってしまったら
If I hold your hand,
孤独を知らないこの街には
to this town that knows no loneliness
もう二度と帰ってくることはできないのだろう
I probably won't be able to return ever again.
君が手を差し伸べた 光で影が生まれる
You reached out your hand, and light gives birth to shadow.
歌って聞かせて この話の続き
Sing and let me hear the rest of this story,
連れて行って 見たこともない星まで
take me to a star I've never seen before.
誰の手も声も届かない 高くそびえ立つ塔の上へ
To the top of the tower rising high where no one's hand or voice can reach,
飛ばすフウセンカズラ
launching balloon vines,
僕は君に笑って欲しいんだ
I want you to smile.
満たされない穴は 惰性の会話や
The unfilled void is filled with idle chatter
澄ましいたポーズで これまでは埋めてきたけれど
and poised poses that I've used to patch things up until now, but
退屈な日々を蹴散らして
kicking away these boring days,
君と二人で この街中を泳いだら 素敵なことでしょう?
if the two of us swam through this town together, wouldn't that be wonderful?
出したことないほど大きな声で
With a voice louder than I've ever used,
やっと君に伝わる
I finally convey it to you.
歪(いびつ)なくらいが きっとちょうどいいね
A distortedness is surely just right.
世界の端と端を結んで
Connecting the ends of the world together,
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって ひとり宇宙を旅をして
Tracing the painting on the window, traveling the universe alone—
それだけでも不自由ないけど 僕は選んでみたいの
even if that alone is free of hardship, I want to choose...
高鳴る心 謎だらけの空を
A throbbing heart, the sky full of mysteries,
安全なループを 今、書き換えて!
rewriting the safe loop right now!
君の手を握ってしまったら
If I hold your hand,
孤独を知らない この街にはもう二度と帰ってくることはできないのだろう
I probably won't be able to return to this town that knows no loneliness ever again.
いくらでも迷いながら
No matter how much I wander,
光も影も見に行こう
let's go see both light and shadow.
歌って聞かせて この話の続き
Sing and let me hear the rest of this story,
連れて行って 見たこともない星まで
take me to a star I've never seen before.
世界の端と端を結んで
Connecting the ends of the world together.
歌って 歌って 聞かせて
Sing, sing, and let me hear,
この話の続き 連れて行って
take me along with the rest of this story
見たこともない 星まで
to a star I've never seen before.
世界の端と端を結んで
Connecting the ends of the world together.
はーい、というわけでね！
Hii! So, um!
本日のご起立、
Today's standing ovation,
オレンジ担当みんなの心の、お寿司のご起立！
everyone's favorite orange representative, Nene Sushi, please stand!
まずはねねスシ！
First, Nene Sushi!
皆さん、ねねちライブにようこそー！
Everyone, welcome to Nenechi's live!
みんな見て、今日ステージがこれ初お披露目になります！
Look everyone, this is the very first time we're revealing this stage!
見て、青い空に、えっと、木と、
Look, the blue sky, um, trees,
あとフェンスと、あと、えっと、蝶々と、えっと、虫！
and fences, um, butterflies, and, um, bugs!
すごい！風船、ねねの風船と、猫の皆の風船と、いっぱいあります！
Amazing! There are so many balloons—Nene's balloons, and all the cats' balloons!
そして桃ねねの2番のところで、みんなに、えっと、初めてお披露目したバズーカ砲！みんなにサインボール、キャッチできた人はいたでしょうか！
And during the second verse of "Momone-ne", I debuted the bazooka cannon for the first time! I wonder if anyone managed to catch a signed ball!
何人かのおうちの人にはきっとね、あのバーチャルごしにぶってこうボールが飛んできてキャッチできたんじゃないかなと思います！
I'm sure for some of you at home, a ball flew right through the virtual screen and you managed to catch it!
さあ、今日のタグなんですけど、今日は「桃鈴ねねの4周年」これでいきたいと思いますので、サインボール捕まええた人は、え、可愛いねねがね、あのいっぱい撮れた人も、あのいっぱいツイートしてくれると嬉しいです！
Now, for today's hashtag, it's "#MomosuzuNene4thAnniversary". I'd love it if those of you who caught a signed ball, or those who took lots of cute pictures of Nene, could tweet about it lots!
さあ今回のライブは可愛いねね、かっこいいねね、うん、セクシーなねねが、いっぱい、あ、やめて、やめてください！あ、いっぱいいっぱい見られる仕様となっております！
Now, this live concert features cute Nene, cool Nene, um, sexy Nene—wait, stop, please stop! Ah, it's designed so you can see so, so much of it!
というわけで、色々なゲストの方にも来ていただいてますので、ハッシュタグつけていっぱいいお寿司とって共有してください！
So, various guests have also come to join us, so please add the hashtag, take lots of sushi photos, and share them!
ぱい ぴぴ ぺぺ ぽぱっぴーぱい ぺぱっぴ
Pai pipi pepe popappy pai pepappi
空は飛べないけれど 夢のツバサがある
Though I can't fly in the sky, I have the wings of a dream.
だから POTA POTA 汗水流して PAKU PAKU
So sweat it out, POTA POTA, and eat up, PAKU PAKU!
大きく育て いつか大空を制すのだ!
Grow big and eventually conquer the open skies!
天高く羽ばたいて 最高よりも高く
Rise up and soar high into the blue sky,
さあ行こう！ひろがる世界へと プリキュア
Let's go to a wide-open world, Pretty Cure!
雨上がりにかかる虹のプリズム
Clouds break apart from silver linings into rainbows,
何かが始まる空の気配（ソラノケハイ）
This could be the start of something new.
確かめるように手を伸ばしたら
Reaching to grab on and see,
希望という光つかんでいた秒でキャッチ！
Pursuing it, standing tall!
絶望を越えて（越えて）わたしたちは強くなる
Moving beyond all despair, we grow stronger.
涙を拭いて
Wipe away all your tears,
（are you ready? go）take off（ユウキノツバサデ）
Are you ready? Go, take off!
天高く羽ばたいて 最高ノココロイキ
Rise up and soar high into the blue sky,
イライラもキラキラに変えてして
Stronger than mountains, song, and dancing lights.
未の世界 未来図は可能性でいっぱい
Be brave and know the future's bright!
同じ空 つながる仲間
With your hand in mine, and basking under the sky,
明日へ続（つづ）け！キセキ
We'll make a miracle from disbelief!
雨上がりにかかる虹のプリズム
Clouds break apart from silver linings into rainbows,
何かが始まる空の気配
This could be the start of something new.
確かめるように手を伸ばしたら
Reaching to grab on and see,
希望という光つかんでいた秒でキャッチ！
Pursuing it, standing tall!
絶望を越えて（越えて）わたしたちは強くなる
Moving beyond all despair, we grow stronger.
ひろがるスカイ！プリキュア
Soaring through the sky, Pretty Cure!
天高く羽ばたいて 最高ノココロイキ
Rise up and soar high into the blue sky,
イライラもキラキラに変えてして
Stronger than mountains, song, and dancing lights.
未の世界 未来図は可能性でいっぱい
Be brave and know the future's bright!
同じ空 つながる仲間
With your hand in mine, and basking under the sky,
明日へ続（つづ）け！キセキ
We'll make a miracle from disbelief!
雨上がりにかかる虹のプリズム
Clouds break apart from silver linings into rainbows,
何かが始まる空の気配
This could be the start of something new.
確かめるように手を伸ばしたら
Reaching to grab on and see,
希望という光つかんでいた秒でキャッチ！
Pursuing it, standing tall!
絶望を越えて（越えて）わたしたちは強くなる
Moving beyond all despair, we grow stronger.
涙を拭いて
Wipe away all your tears,
（are you ready? go）take off（ユウキノツバサデ）
Are you ready? Go, take off!
天高く羽ばたいて 最高ノココロイキ
Rise up and soar high into the blue sky,
イライラもキラキラに変えてして
Stronger than mountains, song, and dancing lights.
未の世界 未来図は可能性でいっぱい
Be brave and know the future's bright!
同じ空 つながる仲間
With your hand in mine, and basking under the sky,
明日へ続（つづ）け！キセキ
We'll make a miracle from disbelief!
雨上がりにかかる虹のプリズム
Clouds break apart from silver linings into rainbows,
何かが始まる空の気配
This could be the start of something new.
確かめるように手を伸ばしたら
Reaching to grab on and see,
希望という光つかんでいた秒でキャッチ！
Pursuing it, standing tall!
絶望を越えて（越えて）わたしたちは強くなる
Moving beyond all despair, we grow stronger.
ひろがるスカイ！プリキュア
Soaring through the sky, Pretty Cure!
天高く羽ばたいて 最高ノココロイキ
Rise up and soar high into the blue sky,
イライラもキラキラに変えてして
Stronger than mountains, song, and dancing lights.
未の世界 未来図は可能性でいっぱい
Be brave and know the future's bright!
同じ空 つながる仲間
With your hand in mine, and basking under the sky,
明日へ続（つづ）け！キセキ
We'll make a miracle from disbelief!
雨上がりにかかる虹のプリズム
Clouds break apart from silver linings into rainbows,
何かが始まる空の気配
This could be the start of something new.
確かめるように手を伸ばしたら
Reaching to grab on and see,
希望という光つかんでいた秒でキャッチ！
Pursuing it, standing tall!
絶望を越えて（越えて）わたしたちは強くなる
Moving beyond all despair, we grow stronger.
涙を拭いて
Wipe away all your tears,
（are you ready? go）take off（ユウキノツバサデ）
Are you ready? Go, take off!
天高く羽ばたいて 最高ノココロイキ
Rise up and soar high into the blue sky,
イライラもキラキラに変えてして
Stronger than mountains, song, and dancing lights.
未の世界 未来図は可能性でいっぱい
Be brave and know the future's bright!
同じ空 つながる仲間
With your hand in mine, and basking under the sky,
明日へ続（つづ）け！キセキ
We'll make a miracle from disbelief!
雨上がりにかかる虹のプリズム
Clouds break apart from silver linings into rainbows,
何かが始まる空の気配
This could be the start of something new.
確かめるように手を伸ばしたら
Reaching to grab on and see,
希望という光つかんでいた秒でキャッチ！
Pursuing it, standing tall!
絶望を越えて（越えて）わたしたちは強くなる
Moving beyond all despair, we grow stronger.
涙を拭いて
Wipe away all your tears,
（are you ready? go）take off（ユウキノツバサデ）
Are you ready? Go, take off!
天高く羽ばたいて 最高ノココロイキ
Rise up and soar high into the blue sky,
イライラもキラキラに変えてして
Stronger than mountains, song, and dancing lights.
未の世界 未来図は可能性でいっぱい
Be brave and know the future's bright!
同じ空 つながる仲間
With your hand in mine, and basking under the sky,
明日へ続（つづ）け！キセキ
We'll make a miracle from disbelief!
我々！(うー!)寄り寄り!(にゃー!)
Wareware! Yore yore!
世界はDark!(こずみっく!)
Sekai wa Dark!
心ぬるぬる異形の神々
Deformed gods with slimy hearts,
私もあなたも怖がりのものずき
Both you and I are curious cowards.
形むるむる異教徒逃げれば
If weird cultists run away,
私とあなたはおでてんかでおでーと
You and I will have a date under the blazing sun!
たのしいね焼けるぞ溶けるぞ(生き物じゃなーい)
It's so much fun, roasting and melting away!
骸（むくろ）ひやひや其れでも好きです
Skeletons feel cold, but I still love you.
私が一番欲しいのはナイショよ
What I want most is a secret!
姿ぱやぱや其れでは行きましょう
Vague appearance, let's get going then.
私に一番似合うかな不条理
What suits me best must be absurdity.
鏡には(だんだん誰なの?)うつらない(誰なんだ?やだやだ)
I don't show up in the mirror...
欲望は言葉にしなくちゃ(うー!)
Desires have to be put into words!
ほら(にゃー!)消えちゃうでしょう?(れっつにゃー!)
See, they'd just disappear, wouldn't they?
我々！(うー！)
We are! (Ooh!)
寄り依り！(にゃー！)
Gathering close! (Meow!)
世界はDark！(こずみっく！)
The world is Dark! (Cosmic!)
心和むる 異形の神々
Eldritch deities soothing the heart,
私もあなたも 畏れの物ずき
both you and I are freaks of fear.
形貌異教徒 逃げれば
If strange heretics try to run away,
私とあなたはおデート
you and I will have a date under the blazing sun!
たのしいね 焼けるぞ 溶けるぞ
Fun, is it? Burning, melting away...
(生き物じゃなーい)
(Not even living things!)
骨ひやひや 其れでも好きです
Bones chilling, yet I still love it.
私がいちばん欲しいのは内緒よ
What I want most of all is a secret.
姿ぱやぱや 其れでは行けません
Flashing forms, you can't go on like that.
私にいちばん似合うかな不条理
What suits me best might just be absurdity.
鏡には(だん だん 誰なの?)
In the mirror... (Step by step, who is it?)
うつらない(誰なんだ? やだよやだよ)
Doesn't reflect (Who is it? No, no, no!)
欲望は 言葉にしなくちゃ(うー!)
Desires must be put into words! (Ooh!)
ほら(にゃー!) 消えにしちゃうでしょ?(レッツにゃー!)
Look, (Meow!) they'll disappear, won't they? (Let's meow!)
太陽なんか 眩しくて 闇のほうが無限です
The sun is too dazzling, the darkness is infinite!
太陽ばっか 眩しくて 闇のほうが す・て・き
The sun is dazzlingly bright, darkness is so wonderful!
CAOS CAOS I wanna CAOS 燃えよ混沌 無敵です
CAOS CAOS I wanna CAOS, burn, chaos, we are invincible!
CAOS CAOS una sera CAOS 燃えるような き・も・ち
CAOS CAOS una sera CAOS, a burning feeling!
我々！(うー！)
We are! (Ooh!)
遣り破れ！(にゃー！)
Breaking through! (Meow!)
世界はDark！(こずみっく！)
The world is Dark! (Cosmic!)
枕ぽかぽか 無貌の神々
Pillows fluffy, faceless deities,
私とあなたとは 目的は違うの
you and I have different purposes.
絡むかむか 無理矢理されがち
Entangling, getting forced into it,
私があなたを守るけどおピンチ
I protect you, but it's an emergency!
おかしいな 逃げるぞ 吠えるぞ(狙われてるー!)
Strange, running away, howling... (Being targeted!)
帳おりおり 此処まで来ました
Curtains falling, we've come this far.
私はだまって 敵たちを蹂躙する
Silently, I trample upon our enemies.
燔りめめめ 此処では駄目です
Cremating, no, not here!
私にだまって スカウトはしないで
Don't scout behind my back!
望むなら(ぜん ぜん 全滅!)
If you wish for it... (Total annihilation!)
しましょうね(敵なんだ? やれやれ)
Let's do it. (An enemy? Good grief.)
願わくば 跡形もなくね(うー!)
Hopefully leaving no trace behind! (Ooh!)
あら(にゃー!) 要らないでしょ?(レッツにゃー!)
My, (Meow!) you don't need it, do you? (Let's meow!)
現在なんと危険だった 光りものを下さに
It was so dangerous just now, bring me something shining!
現在なんと危険だった 光りもので刺激して
It was so dangerous just now, stimulate me with something shining!
待て待て要要待て 呼べばボードかげきって
Wait, wait, wait, summon and rock it out!
待て待てあんま待て 呼べばきっとおしまい!
Wait, wait, don't wait too much, summon it and it's over!
はいよるこんどうぅ にゃるらとほー
Haiyore Konduu Nyarlathotep!
太陽なんか眩しくて 闇のほうが無限です
The sun is too dazzling, the darkness is infinite!
太陽ばっか眩しくて 闇のほうが す・て・き
The sun is dazzlingly bright, darkness is so wonderful!
CAOS CAOS I wanna CAOS 燃えよ混沌 無敵です
CAOS CAOS I wanna CAOS, burn, chaos, we are invincible!
CAOS CAOS una sera CAOS 燃えるような き・も・ち
CAOS CAOS una sera CAOS, a burning feeling!
我々！(うー！) 寄り依り！(にゃー！)
We are! (Ooh!) Gathering close! (Meow!)
世界はDark！(こずみっく！)
The world is Dark! (Cosmic!)
心和むる異形の神々
Eldritch deities soothing the heart,
私もあなたも畏れの物ずき
both you and I are freaks of fear.
形貌異教徒逃げれば
If strange heretics try to run away,
私とあなたはおデート
you and I will have a date under the blazing sun!
たのしいね 焼けるぞ 溶けるぞ(生き物じゃなーい)
Fun, is it? Burning, melting away... (Not even living things!)
骨ひやひや 其れでも好きです
Bones chilling, yet I still love it.
私がいちばん欲しいのは内緒よ
What I want most of all is a secret.
姿ぱやぱや 其れでは行けません
Flashing forms, you can't go on like that.
私にいちばん似合うかな不条理
What suits me best might just be absurdity.
鏡には(だん だん 誰なの?)
In the mirror... (Step by step, who is it?)
うつらない(誰なんだ? やだよやだよ)
Doesn't reflect (Who is it? No, no, no!)
欲望は言葉にしなくちゃ(うー!)
Desires must be put into words! (Ooh!)
ほら(nゃー!) 消えにしちゃうでしょ?(レッツにゃー!)
Look, (Meow!) they'll disappear, won't they? (Let's meow!)
太陽なんか眩しくて 闇のほうが無限です
The sun is too dazzling, the darkness is infinite!
太陽ばっか眩しくて 闇のほうが す・て・き
The sun is dazzlingly bright, darkness is so wonderful!
CAOS CAOS I wanna CAOS 燃えよ混沌 無敵です
CAOS CAOS I wanna CAOS, burn, chaos, we are invincible!
CAOS CAOS una sera CAOS 燃えるような き・も・ち
CAOS CAOS una sera CAOS, a burning feeling!
太陽なんか眩しくて 闇のほうが無限です
The sun is too dazzling, the darkness is infinite!
太陽ばっか眩しくて 闇のほうが す・て・き
The sun is dazzlingly bright, darkness is so wonderful!
CAOS CAOS I wanna CAOS 燃えよ混沌 無敵です
CAOS CAOS I wanna CAOS, burn, chaos, we are invincible!
CAOS CAOS una sera CAOS 燃えるような き・も・ち
CAOS CAOS una sera CAOS, a burning feeling!
はいよるこんどうぅ にゃるらとほー
Haiyore Konduu Nyarlathotep!
わかってるっしょ？ わかってる 欲しいんでしょ？
You know, right? You know you want it, right?
艶やかな この唇
This glossy pair of lips
ヤワな 男たち 惹き寄せる
draws in timid men.
息を呑む ほどに 甘い密
Sweet nectar that takes your breath away,
わかってるっしょ？ わかってる 欲しいんでしょ？
You know, right? You know you want it, right?
二度見する この身体
This body that makes people look twice,
汗ばむ 街 一人 歩けば
walking alone through the sweaty town.
淫らな 視線が 絡みつく
Lewd gazes entangle around me.
ねえ 何を 期待して るの？
Hey, what are you expecting?
そのうち じゃなくて 今すぐ がいいの
Not eventually, I want it right now.
大人の 恋に 焦がれて
Yearning for adult love,
見た目 より も 残る あどけない
more innocent than it looks, leaving a trace.
(Ah) 心 だけ が (Ah) 先走る
(Ah) Only my heart races ahead,
青い 蕾 の まま 大人 振る舞う
acting grown-up while still a blue bud.
わかってるっしょ？ わかってる 欲しいんでしょ？
You know, right? You know you want it, right?
刺激する 私の 全て
Everything about me is stimulating,
冷めた 瞳 まで 魅了する
charming even those cold eyes.
いつかは 花 に なる アメリリス
Someday I'll become a flower, Amaryllis.
優しい だけ の 言葉 じゃなくて
Not just gentle words,
心で 繋がり たくて
I want us to connect by heart.
ありきたりな メイク じゃ 隠せない
Can't hide it with ordinary makeup.
(Ah) 憧れ だけ (Ah) 夢 を 見る
(Ah) Just longing, (Ah) dreaming dreams,
あなた の 前 で また 大人 振る舞う
acting grown-up again in front of you.
そのうち じゃなくて 今すぐ がいいの
Not eventually, I want it right now.
大人の 恋に 焦がれて
Yearning for adult love,
見た目 より も 残る あどけない
more innocent than it looks, leaving a trace.
(Ah) 気持ち だけ が (Ah) から回り
(Ah) Only my feelings misfire,
私 を 見つめて
looking at me.
優しい だけ の 言葉 じゃなくて
Not just gentle words...
わかってる ほしいんでしょ？
You know what I want, don't you?
艶やかな この唇
These alluring lips of mine
ヤワな男たち 惹き寄せる
Draw in fragile men
息を吸うほどに 甘い蜜
Sweet nectar that takes your breath away
わかってる ほしいんでしょ？
You know what I want, don't you?
二度見する この身なり
Making people look twice at my appearance
オトナブルー
Otona Blue
そのうちじゃなくて 今すぐがいいの
Not someday, I want it right now
大人の恋に焦がれて
Yearning for adult love
見た目よりも残る あどけない
Remaining more innocent than it looks
気持ちだけが空回り
My feelings just spin out of control
私を見つめて
Look at me
優しいだけの言葉じゃなくて
Not just kind words,
心で繋がりたくて
I want to connect from the heart
ありきたりな メイクじゃ 隠せない
Can't hide it with ordinary makeup
憧れだけ
Just yearning,
夢を見る
Dreaming a dream
あなたの前で また大人振る
Acting like an adult again in front of you
オトナブルー
Otona Blue
未熟 無秩序 されど美しくあれ
Inexperienced, disordered, but be beautiful
No Destiny ふさわしくない
No Destiny, it doesn't fit
こんなんじゃきっと物足りない
This surely isn't enough
くらい語っとけばうまくいく
If I talk like that, it'll work out
物、金、愛、言、もう自己顕示欲飽和
Things, money, love, words, ego is saturated
既視感何がそんな不満なんだ?
What on earth is so dissatisfying about dejà vu?
散々わがまま語ってて これ以上他に何がいる?
Saying whatever selfish things you want, what else do you need?
中途半端だけは嫌
I hate being half-hearted
もういい
Enough!
ああしてこうして言ってたって
Even if you say do this and do that,
愛してどうして? 言われたって
Even if you ask why love me?
遊びだけなら簡単で
It's easy if it's just play,
真剣交渉無茶苦茶で
But serious negotiation is a mess
思いもしない軽い言葉 何度使い回すのか?
How many times will you reuse those thoughtless words?
どうせ期待してたんだ出来レースでも
Anyway, I was hoping for it even if it's a fixed race
引用だらけのフレーズも 自尊持ち上がる言葉タブーにして
Tabooing phrases full of quotes that boost pride
空気読んだ雨降らないでよ
Read the room, don't let it rain
もう何年も前の話し合いは
Discussions from years ago
必要最低限で現実に虹はいらないよ
The bare minimum, I don't need a rainbow in reality
暗い夜中はなんの目ももう送らない
Pitch black nights won't send any more eyes
脆い扇子広げるその方が魅力的でしょう迷いで
Spreading a fragile fan, that's more attractive, isn't it?
メイで答えられないならほっといて
If you can't answer, just leave me alone
迷えるくらいならさっといて
If you're going to hesitate, get out of here
肝心なとこは筒抜けで
The crucial parts leak right through
安心だけはさせられるような
Bringing peace of mind
だから
Therefore,
それでもいいからさ
Even so, it's fine,
ここにいたいよ
I want to stay here
もういい
Enough!
ああしてこうして言ってたって
Even if you say do this and do that,
愛してどうして? 言われたって
Even if you ask why love me?
遊びだけなら簡単で
It's easy if it's just play,
神経交渉無茶苦茶で
But nervous negotiations are a mess
思いもしない軽い言葉
Thoughtless words
いつか笑い合えるように
So we can smile together one day
未熟 無ジょう されど 美しくあれ
Immature and heartless, yet be beautiful.
No Destiny ふさわしくない
No Destiny, it's just not fitting.
こんなんじゃきっと物足りない
This surely isn't enough.
今日も 雨
Today, too, it rains.
傘を 閉じて
Closing my umbrella,
濡れて 帰ろうよ
Let's go home soaking wet.
魂の色は 何色ですか
What color is your soul?
もう凍れたままで
Staying frozen like this,
捨てるほど 逃げ出すほど
So much that I want to throw it away, to run away,
強くないよ ほら
I'm not strong, you see.
もう一度鼓動 高鳴る
Beating once again, heart pounding,
何が正しいからって
wondering what is right.
わからないけど
Even though I don't know,
形のないものばかりが 大切になっていく
Only things without shape become precious.
飾らない言葉だけが 強く結ばれてる
Only unadorned words are tightly bound together.
また躓いて 転がって それでも砕けない
Stumbling and rolling again, yet never breaking.
魂の色は 何色ですか
What color is your soul?
ただ傷ついて 強がって それでも見つけたいよ
Just getting hurt, acting tough, yet still wanting to find it.
魂のカタチ 確かめているよ
I am confirming the shape of my soul.
深い地の底で一人 扉と鍵を探す
Alone at the bottom of the deep earth, searching for a door and key.
おとぎ話は ほら 泡の様に全部消えて
Fairy tales, you see, all vanish like bubbles,
葛藤 残像だけ 次のページへ
leaving conflict and afterimages, moving to the next page.
伸びてく枝葉が分かれて それぞれの道を行く
Growing branches split apart, each going their own way.
寂しい思い出だけが 強く根を張っている
Only lonely memories have deep, strong roots.
また貫いて 失って それでも挫けない
Piercing through and losing again, yet still not giving up.
心はどこに 器はどこに
Where is the heart? Where is the vessel?
ただ残されて抜け落ちて それでも伝えたいよ
Just left behind and falling out, yet I still want to convey it.
魂の日々を 魂の意志を ずっと
The days of the soul, the will of the soul, forever.
魂の色は 何色ですか 赤色ですか 青色ですか
What color is the soul? Is it red? Is it blue?
魂の色は 何色ですか
What color is the soul?
何色ですか
What color is it?
赤色ですか
Is it red?
青色ですか
Is it blue?
魂の色は 魂の色は 何色ですか 何色ですか
What color is the soul? What color is the soul?
透明な過去に 不透明な明日に 生きるあなたは何色ですか
In a transparent past and opaque tomorrow, what color are you living in?
涙が止まらないよ 歩きながら溢れる
Tears won't stop as I walk, they overflow
人混みに紛れても この悲しみ 隠せない
Even lost in the crowd, I can't hide this sadness
賑わっていたスーパーで あなたと彼女 見かけたの
At the bustling supermarket, I saw you and her
楽しそうに 買い物する 腕を組む2人
Shopping happily, arms linked together
愛は 何色 どんな色 AH-誰かの色
What color is love, what color? Ah, someone's color
心は 今揺れながら プリズムようなもの
My heart trembling now like a prism
もっと 信じてみたかった AH-私の色
I wanted to try believing more, ah, my color
この世に そう ひた一つの 大事な愛の色
In this world, yes, the only precious color of love
あまり容赦しないで
Don't go too easy on me
私だって不景気
I've got my hard times too
公式なんて要らない
I don't need any formulas
好きな解答が欲しい
I want the answer I like
よそ行きに毎日
Every day dressed up
染まれて不安でしょう
Dyed and feeling insecure, right?
そんな目で気にしないで
Don't look at me like that
ハッピーエンドの小説みたいで素敵じゃない
It's like a happy ending novel, isn't that nice?
好きな解答が欲しい
I want the answer I like
よそ行きに毎日
Every day dressed up
染まれて不安でしょう
Dyed and feeling insecure, right?
好きな歌なら歌いたい
If it's my favorite song, I want to sing it
欲しいものなら全部持ってると思ったけど足りない
I thought I had everything I wanted, but it's not enough
私の想像超えて
Surpassing my imagination
ああ!
Ah!
叫ぶ I need you
I shout I need you
間近な glitter
Imminent glitter
気に入らないの
I don't like it
燃えるように競い咲いてるも
Even blooming in rivalry like burning fire
freezing!
なんて言ったってフリーキー
Whatever you say, it's freaking awesome
i guess you're right, darling
そんなんじゃ私には分からない
Like that, I don't understand
行ったり来たりしないで 簡単なことよ
Don't go back and forth, it's simple
居場所は忘れましょう
Let's forget our place
明日も少女でいたい 裏腹に自分を
I want to be a girl tomorrow too, while going against myself
邪魔してやまない 中途半端で居られない
Constantly disturbing, I can't stay half-assed
痛いことならいつも待っていると分かっているから
Because I know it always hurts when waiting
待たない かかってこいよ baby
Won't wait, bring it on baby
ああ! 出でよ fire
Ah! Come forth, fire
空前絶後の movement
Unprecedented movement
言い訳はしないで
Don't make excuses
燃えるような私を見てよ
Look at me burning up
screaming!
本当は naked
Truly naked
i think you're just a hero
今のあなたはつまらない
You are boring now
行ったり来たりしないで 簡単なことよ
Don't go back and forth, it's simple
居場所は忘れましょう
Let's forget our place
明日も少女でいたい 裏腹に自分を
I want to be a girl tomorrow too, while going against myself
邪魔してやまない 中途半端で居られない
Constantly disturbing, I can't stay half-assed
痛いことならいつも待っていると分かっているから
Because I know it always hurts when waiting
待たない かかってこいよ baby
Won't wait, bring it on baby
中途半端でいられない
Can't stay half-assed
痛いことなら いつも待っていると分かっているから
Because I know you're always waiting for something painful
待たない かかってこいよ baby
Won't wait, bring it on baby
ああ! 会いたいよ早く
Ah! I want to see you soon
全然てんてんこの胸で言い訳はしないで
Not at all in this heart, don't make excuses
燃えるような私を見てよ
Look at me burning up
好きならスキミ本当はできない
If you like it, really you can't
アイチェンジャスタヒーロー
I changed just a hero
今のあなたはつまらない
You are boring now
ああ! 叫ぶ I need you
Ah! I shout I need you
間近な glitter
Imminent glitter
気に入らないの
I don't like it
燃えるように競い咲いてるも
Even blooming in rivalry like burning fire
freezing!
なんて言ったってフリーキー 確かに好みじゃないわ
Whatever you say, it's freaking awesome, certainly not my type
燃えるような瞳をしてるでしょ
You have burning eyes, don't you?
絶対零度の fever こんな一大事 よそ行きは捨てて迎えに来て
Zero degree fever, such a serious affair, throw away your polite guise and come pick me up
もっとねりべいふたりふたりべいびー
More... baby, both of us baby
たったらだったた とったらだったた ...
Tat-ta-la dat-ta-la...
いぇあー！
Yeah!
どうだった？ねぇのプロみたいな演奏は！
How was that? Like a pro's performance!
今日見てみんなこれ！ねぇねぇ専用のギターを用意してもらいまして！もらいました！
Look at this everyone! I had a custom Nene guitar prepared for me!
かっこいいでしょ？もう凄いソロパートも弾けちゃうんだから！テュルルルル...
Cool, right? I can even play amazing solo parts! Tyurururu...
このかっこいいローアングルを用意してもらっちゃったんだから。
They prepared this cool low angle for me.
さぁみんなゲストパートいかがでしたでしょうかーい！
Now everyone, how was the guest part?!
いろんなあのソロ面と、あの、ああいうの歌ったら凄いいいんじゃないかなーとか色々考えながら、選びましたー！
I thought about all the solo aspects and what would sound great before choosing!
さぁそしてゲストの、あの、こう、サムネイルにいたけど、まだ出てきてないホロメンがいますよね！いつもの人たちをお呼びしたいと思います！
And now, for the guests who were on the thumbnail but haven't appeared yet! Let's invite the usual crew!
ちょっとね...あーごめん！今いくねん！どん！
Wait... Ah sorry! I'm coming now! Boom!
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin’ 飛び出そう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump out!
come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine bright!
ハート きゅって pump it up
Heart squeezed tight, pump it up!
hyper jumpin’ 夢 の 先 まで
Hyper jumpin', right up to our dreams!
もっと もっと
More and more,
刺激 が 欲しい の
we want more thrills!
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin’
Hyper jumpin'
子ども くらい はしゃぐ 方 が お得 でしょ
Acting like a kid pays off more!
低気圧 から 抜け上がっていく テンション
Breaking through low pressure, rising high!
酔い ながら 打ち返し まくる メンション
Batting back mentions while feeling dizzy!
カート を 乗りこなし て 進む ミッション
Riding karts through every mission!
この まま スピード 加速 し て
Speeding up even more just like this,
たどり着く 先 に 何 が ある ん だろ
what awaits us at the end of the road?
止まら ない 気持ち は 助走 つけ て
Unstoppable feelings get a running start,
次元 を 超え て 行こ う さぁ
let's cross over dimensions, come on!
hyper jumpin’ 飛び跳ねよ う
Hyper jumpin', let's jump around!
ハイ に なっ て 灰 に なる まで
Getting so high we turn to ash,
ダンシング shake it up
dancing, shake it up!
hyper jumpin’ 空 の 向こう まで
Hyper jumpin', way beyond the sky,
もっと もっと 近づき たい の
we want to get closer and closer!
(woh...) ドキドキ し たい
(Woh...) We want our hearts to race,
gimme gimme gimme 愛
gimme gimme gimme love!
(woh...) もっと もっと 高く 飛び たい の
(Woh...) We want to fly even higher!
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin’
Hyper jumpin'
斜め から 攻め て 解決 クエスチョン
Attacking questions from an angle,
ネガティブ を 切り裂い て くれる チェンソー
a chainsaw slicing through negativity!
流れる コメント と 掛け合い セッション
A session interacting with scrolling comments,
エイム を 鍛え て 狙い撃つ flick shot
training aim for a flick shot!
dis は no no 好き なら more more more
Dis is no no, if you like it, more more more!
邪魔 する ノイズ は 撃ち消せ bang bang bang
Shoot down distracting noise, bang bang bang!
遊び たい だけ アンチ は 無視 し て
We just want to play, ignore the antis,
笑い 飛ばし て 踊り飛ばせ
laugh it off and dance away!
kick it !!
Kick it!!
jump around !!
Jump around!!
この まま 僕ら は 旅 を し て
Continuing our journey just like this,
たどり着く 先 に 何 が ある ん だろ
what awaits us at the end of the road?
信じ た 未来 と リンク し て
Linking up with the future we believed in,
次元 を 超え て 行こ う さぁ
let's cross over dimensions, come on!
hyper jumpin’ 飛び超えよ う
Hyper jumpin', let's leap across!
ハイ に なっ て 灰 に なる まで
Getting so high we turn to ash,
ダンシング shake it up
dancing, shake it up!
hyper jumpin’ 海 の 向こう まで
Hyper jumpin', way across the sea,
もっと もっと 近づき たい の
we want to get closer and closer!
(woh...) ドキドキ し たい
(Woh...) We want our hearts to race,
gimme gimme gimme 愛
gimme gimme gimme love!
(woh...) もっと もっと 高く 飛び たい の
(Woh...) We want to fly even higher!
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin’
Hyper jumpin'
エイム を 鍛え て 狙い撃つ フリクション
Training aim to strike true, friction!
好き なら もっと もっと
If you love it, more and more,
邪魔 する ノイズ は 撃ち消せ バンバンバン
shoot down annoying noise, bang bang bang!
安心 安心 し て 笑い 飛ばし て
Rest easy and laugh it all off,
蹴っ飛ばせ kick it jump around !!
kick it away, kick it, jump around!!
この まま もっかい 生まれ変わり を し て
Being reborn once again just like this,
たどり着く 先 に 何 が ある ん だろ
what awaits us at the end of the road?
信じ た 未来 と リンク し て
Linking up with the future we believed in,
次元 を 超え て 行こ う さぁ
let's cross over dimensions, come on!
hyper jumpin’ 飛び超えよ う
Hyper jumpin', let's leap across!
ハイ に なっ て 灰 に なる まで
Getting so high we turn to ash,
ダンシング shake it up
dancing, shake it up!
hyper jumpin’ 海 の 向こう まで
Hyper jumpin', way across the sea,
もっと もっと 近づき たい の
we want to get closer and closer!
恥ずかしいの
It's so embarrassing
ドキドキしたい
I want my heart to race
君君君愛
You, you, you, love!
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
ハイパーじゃぴなう
Hyper jumpin' now!
子どもくらいはしゃぐ方がお徳でしょ
It pays to play as carefree as a child,
低気圧から這い上がっていくテンション
climbing up from low pressure spirits.
酔いながら打ち返し捲るメンション
Drunk on momentum, returning every mention,
カートを乗りこなして進むミッション
mastering karts to push through missions.
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating the speed just like this,
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
what awaits us at the end of the road?
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
With our unstoppable feelings gaining momentum,
次元を超えて行こうさあ
let's cross dimensions now!
ハイパーじゃぴん飛び跳ねよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump around!
じゃあ自己紹介しますね
Now, let's do self-introductions.
色自己紹介
Various self-introductions!
このライブがきてね
This live came, and
パラボナ可愛くて
Parabona is so cute,
ヒール担当桃鈴ねね
heal role Momosuzu Nene,
ねねきゅんきゅん
Nene-kyun kyun!
みんなの心のエナジードリンク
Everyone's heart's energy drink,
チュウも言わされたねんね
and made to say 'chu' too, Nene!
さっきの可愛いメンバーは誰かな？
Who were those cute members just now?
え、ねねち、みんなの心のエナジードリンク！
Eh, Nenechi, everyone's heart's energy drink!
エナジードリンク雪花ラミィです！
Snowflake Lamy, energy drink!
心のエナジードリンク雪花ラミィです！
Snowflake Lamy, your heart's energy drink!
雪花ラミィです、ラズチュウ
I'm Lamy Yukihana, Raz-chu-
ラズチュウ、ラズがちゅー！
Raz-chu, Raz gets a chu!
ええじゃあ、心のエナジードリンク獅白ぼたんです！
Eh, well, Shishiro Botan, your heart's energy drink!
本日はお越しいただきましてありがとうございます！
Thank you all so much for coming today!
ハッシュタグ間違いないでね、ハッシュタグ間違えちゃって
Don't get the hashtag wrong, you might mess it up.
4周年じゃなくて、3周年で次4周年だねって話したじゃん！
We talked about how it's not the 4th anniversary, but the 3rd, and next is the 4th!
もう1曲みんなに聞いてほしいななんて思ってますので
We hope you'll listen to one more song from us!
みんな可愛いんだって！ねえ可愛かったよ！
Everyone is so cute! Hey, it was so cute!
じゃあみんな着替えて、もう1曲コメント読みながら
So everyone go change, and we'll read comments while doing one more song!
叩け ボンゴ 響け サンバ
Strike the bongos, let the samba ring,
踊れ 南 の カルナバル
dance to the southern carnival.
誰 も 彼 も 浮かれ 騒ぎ
Everyone's excited and partying away,
光る 汗 が はじけ とぶ
glowing sweat flying and bursting.
熱い 風 に 体 あずけ
Entrusting your body to the hot wind,
心 ゆく まで 踊れ ば
if you dance to your heart's content,
波 も 歌う よ 愛 の サンバ を
even the waves sing the samba of love.
胸 に あふれる この リズム
This rhythm overflowing in our chests,
オーレ オーレ マツケンサンバ
ole, ole, Matsuken Samba!
みなさん、4周年、4周年にやっております
Everyone, we are celebrating our 4th anniversary...
いや、なんとめでたい日にこんな歌を歌ってめでたくなっていこうと思っております
We thought we'd sing a song like this on such a happy day to feel even happier!
みんなガンボンで、あのめだねのことをあの目立たして下さい
Everyone, please make Nene-ne stand out on this happy occasion!
はい、それではねねさいのごと目立たそうと思います
Yes, then I think I'll make Nene-sae stand out too!
始まる！そろそろ始まる！
It's starting! It's starting soon!
打てボンゴ 響けサンバ
Beat the bongos, let the samba ring out,
踊れ 南の カルナバル
Dance the southern carnival!
誰も 彼も 浮かれ 騒ぎ
Everyone is having fun and partying,
光る 汗 が はじけ とぶ
Shimmering sweat flies off!
オーレ！
Olé!
熱い 風 に 体 あずけ
Letting your body drift in the hot wind...
あ、これね、スウィートしてほしい
Ah, make it sweet,
ええ、可愛くしてほしい
Um, make it cute!
あいつ注文多くて…
She has so many demands...
オーレ！オーレ！
Olé! Olé!
打てボンゴ 響けサンバ
Beat the bongos, let the samba ring out,
オーレ！オーレ！
Olé! Olé!
しょうがねえな、打てボンゴ 響けサンバ
Can't be helped. Beat the bongos, let the samba ring out!
踊れセニョリータ、踊れセニョリータ
Dance, señorita, dance, señorita!
さえ忘れて踊りあかそう
Let's forget everything and dance the night away!
サンバ、ビーバサンバ、マツケンサンバ！
Samba, viva samba, Matsuken Samba!
よしよし、いいぞ、いいぞ、この調子
Good, good, looking good, keep it up!
かけていく感じ、めちゃよかったわ
That build-up felt really good!
もう一回スウィートしよう、そうそう
Let's do 'sweet' one more time, yeah, exactly.
大事なとこ… まだありそうだな、おっ
The important part... there's still more, oh!
曲が寄ってっちゃうから無理しないでね
The music is drifting over, so don't push yourselves!
あ、なんか体が寄ってっちゃう
Ah, somehow our bodies are drifting together!
踊れ、ねね！お、すごい、出てくるよ
Dance, Nene! Oh amazing, here they come!
ハート、ハート作ろ！ まだ完成してない！
Let's make a heart! It's not finished yet!
完成系づつだ、コツコツ
Piece by piece, little by little.
まだだよ、まだだよ、今だだよ、それ出す
Not yet, not yet, now, show it!
ねれち、ねれち、もっとコメントも盛り上げて！
Nerechi, Nerechi, hype up the comments more!
さあ、今度はねねの歌い出し、始まります！
Now, Nene's solo opening is starting!
打てボンゴ 響けサンバ
Beat the bongos, let the samba ring out,
踊れ 南の カルナバル
Dance the southern carnival!
夢 の よう に 時 は 過ぎ て
Like a dream, time flies by,
はずむ 南 の 恋 の 夜
The lively southern night of love!
焼けた素肌肩を抱いて
Embracing your sun-kissed skin and shoulders,
愛をささやき踊れば
Whispering love and dancing together,
白い渚に恋も輝き、風に誘われ歌い出す
Love shines bright on the white shore, enticed by the wind, I start to sing!
オーレ！オーレ！
Olé! Olé!
打てボンゴ 響けサンバ
Beat the bongos, let the samba ring out,
オーレ！オーレ！
Olé! Olé!
打てボンゴ 響けサンバ
Beat the bongos, let the samba ring out!
誰さあんまり、踊れセニョリータ、踊れセニョリータさえ忘れて踊りあかそう
Dance, señorita, dance, señorita, let's forget everything and dance the night away!
サンバ、ビーバサンバ、マツケンサンバ！
Samba, viva samba, Matsuken Samba!
打てボンゴ 響けサンバ
Beat the bongos, let the samba ring out!
ありがとう！おめでとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Congratulations! Thank you!
ちょ、かゆい、かゆい、かゆい！
Wait, it's itchy, itchy, itchy!
あ、花火だ！花火の！あ、波のお胸にも花火が！
Ah, fireworks! Fireworks! Ah, fireworks on Nami's chest too!
何言ってるの？
What are you talking about?
どうした？あ、大丈夫か？
What's wrong? Ah, are you okay?
えーと、というわけでみなさん、お水などは大丈夫ですかね？
Uh, so everyone, are you okay with water and stuff?
えーと、というわけでみなさん、あのグッズ周回お付けいただいてもいいですし…よろしくお願いします！
Uh, so everyone, you can check out the goods tour or whatever... thank you very much!
さあ、ここで今回のねね4周年目に向けたオリジナルグッズ紹介です！こちら、じゃじゃーん！
Now, here is the introduction of original goods for Nene's 4th anniversary! Here it is, ta-da!
ねっ子グッズいぇーい！
Nekko merch, yay!
みんなこのイラスト今回のお写真になると
Everyone, this illustration in the photos this time...
おっ！
Oh!
ごみりせんせーです！
It's Gomiri-sensei!
いらすとせせー！いぇーい！
Illust-sensei! Yay!
はい、というわけで最初は こちら！
Right, so first up is this!
だーん！
Ta-da!
え、ねっこのぬいぐるみ キーホルダーになります！
Um, Nekko plushie keychains!
ギシギシ言います。
It squeaks.
え、ねっこのぬいぐるみ2023年バージョンです！
Um, it's the 2023 version of the Nekko plushie!
あれ、どこが違うんでしたっけ？
Wait, how is it different again?
はい、ねっこも成長いたしまして、なんと推しの前でよだれを垂らせるようになったというわけです！
Right, the Nekkos have grown, and now they can drool in front of their oshi!
いやー、すばらしい！
Wow, wonderful!
はい、次！
Right, next!
あれ？わあー！
Huh? Whoa!
これば、第1世代のにんじんねっこのだいこんバージョンです！
This is the daikon version of the 1st-generation carrot Nekko!
え、次第2世代が出るってこと？まだよだれ垂れてないんだね。
Wait, does that mean 2nd gen is coming? They aren't drooling yet.
無限じゃん、じゃあプロとか出てくる？
It's infinite then, will pros start appearing?
色違いね、星付きのプロマックスとか出てくるかも。
Different colors, star-ranked Pro Max might appear.
大きくなっちゃうかもしれない。
They might get bigger.
そして、次ちょっとごめんね、おまーるんがいいなって思って真似しました、どん！
And next, sorry, I thought Omarun's would be nice so I copied it, ta-da!
あっ！
Ah!
ねね推しはっぴ！いいじゃん！いいじゃん！
Nene-oshi Happi! That's great! That's great!
いえーい！いろんなんですか？
Yay! What kind is it?
はい、ねねの推しハッピになります！
Right, it's Nene's oshi happi!
うわあ！いぇーい！
Whoa! Yay!
じゃ、これじゃあ、あとしのらみちゃん出てないじゃん、ハッピ。
Then wait, Lamy-chan isn't out yet, for happi.
そう、あ、そうだよ。これは強制的に、ね、次ハッピ？
That's right, oh yeah. This is forcibly... wait, next happi?
ね、プロボハッピ！暑いよ、これ！
Right, Provo happi! It's hot, this!
作らないといけないね。
We gotta make it.
そういうこと。今回は表と裏でちょっとずつ表情が違うので、よかったらじっくり後で見てみてください！
Exactly. This time the front and back have slightly different expressions, so take your time to check it out later if you'd like!
そして、え、全部揃えてくれた方のセットこちら！じゃーん！
And um, here's the set for those who got everything! Ta-da!
チェキ風の…
Instax-style...
あ、ボイス！
Ah, voice!
あ、そうそう！
Ah, right, right!
ボイス！ボイスもある！どんなボイスなんですか？
Voice! There's voice too! What kind of voice is it?
はい、ねっことお友達と捉えまして、通話のボイスが出ます！
Right, imagining being friends with a Nekko, a phone call voice!
なんと初版とか関係なくて！
And it's not related to first edition or anything!
え、ちょっと、まだね、ちょっと、あの、これからねねの深いにファンになっちゃうかなみたいな人と、まずお友達から始めましょう！
Um, wait, still, for people who might become deep fans of Nene from now on, let's start as friends first!
そして、全部揃えてくれた方こちら！
And, for those who got everything, this!
じゃーん！
Ta-da!
チェキ風のブロマイドカードと特定のボイスが付きます！
It comes with an Instax-style bromide card and a special voice!
詳細こちら！
Here are the details!
はい、今回直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードは表情差分のねねちゃんでーす！
Right, this time the handwritten signed Instax-style bromide card features Nene-chan with different facial expressions!
まさかこれは…
Could this possibly be...
全員に、あ、全員にかきます！
Written for everyone, ah, I'll write for everyone!
はい、そして通話の、あ、じゃないじゃない、特典のボイスが…
Right, and the call, ah no no, the bonus voice...
ま、ちょっとさっきのところから進展がありまして、ま、2人で寝落ち通話なんてしちゃうの。あらあら！
Well, there's been some progress from earlier, like falling asleep on a call together. Oh my!
随分進展しちゃってー。
Quite a lot of progress.
ええ、夜に2人で眠れないよ～
Yeah, at night the two of us can't sleep~
みたいこと言ってるやつが寝落ち通話で寝ちゃってるやつですね。
That kind of thing, someone who says that falls asleep on the call.
そうです、雑音聞きながら寝るやつ。やったー！
That's right, falling asleep while listening to white noise. Yay!
え、そして、え、次が最後の曲になるんですけど、みなさん…
And um, next will be the last song, everyone...
はっ、何ですか？
Huh, what is it?
ねね最近、あの、あれ、あの新曲出したんですよ。
Nene recently, um, released a new song.
おっ！
Oh!
ギラファですね。
Giraffa, right?
あ、ギラファ？
Ah, Giraffa?
ギラファですね。
Giraffa, right?
ギラファなんだ。
Giraffa, huh.
ギラファ、ギラファ？
Giraffa, Giraffa?
ギラファにしようかな。
I'll make it Giraffa.
ギラファ！
Giraffa!
ギラファにしよう！ギラファにしよう！
Let's make it Giraffa! Let's make it Giraffa!
そして、そのMVがもう枠立ってるんですけど、22時15分から公開になります！楽しみだー！
And its MV already has a waiting room set up, and it premieres at 22:15! I'm so excited!
そして、その前に、え、振り付けが、ある、あ、振り付けがあるので…
And before that, um, there's choreography, ah, since there's choreography...
あの、まずはそちらを初を披露してかな、みんなのもとにMVお届けしたいと思ってて、でもこのギラファの、あのMVの後にも…
Um, first I want to debut that choreography and deliver the MV to everyone, but even after this Giraffa MV...
もう一曲ちょっと匂わせあるので、楽しみにしててください！
There's another hint of a song, so please look forward to it!
匂わせ、匂わせ大好きだよね、ほんとにね。
Hints, you really love hints, don't you?
え、じゃあ皆さんありがとうございましたー！お邪魔しましたー！
Um, well everyone, thank you very much! Thanks for having us!
お邪魔しました。ありがとうございましたー！
Thanks for having us. Thank you very much!
お邪魔しましたー！またなー！
Thanks for having us! See ya!
はい、あ、また、いましたおまるんが。
Yes, ah, Omarun is here again.
はーい、というわけでねねも着替えてギラファミーティングみんなと一绪に歌って踊っていきたいと思います！ほな、お着替え！
Alriiight, so Nene will go change and we'll sing and dance to Giraffa Meeting together with everyone! Welp, time to change!
ハッピーギラファ！ねねちのギラギラファンミーティングへようこそ！
Happy Giraffa! Welcome to Nenechi's Giragira Fan Meeting!
さあ！ツノと頬をながーく伸ばして、思いきり楽しんじゃおうね！
Now! Lengthen your horns and cheeks, and let's have as much fun as we can!
それじゃ、いくよ！
Alright then, here we go!
アミーを！かけーろ！
Cast your Amii!
ビバ！ギラファ！
Viva! Giraffa!
ギラギラ最高だね kabu-kuwa
Giragira is the best, kabu-kuwa
クリクリおめめラブ kabu-kuwa
Shiny big-eyed love kabu-kuwa
愛のダンスはムーチョムーチョ跳んで
Love's dance is mucho mucho, jump
シュビドゥバメロメロ
shubiduba melted
みんな集まれゾロゾロ
Everyone gather zoro-zoro
こん^ ^chu☆chu☆
Kon^^ chu☆ chu☆
パヤパヤパヤパパヤ
Paya paya paya paya paya
ギラギラギラファ
Giragira Giraffa
ハッピーギラファーーーッ！
Happy Giragira Fafa~!
ねねちのギラギラファンミーティングへようこそ！
Welcome to Nenechi's Giragira Fan Meeting!
さあ！ツノと頬をなーーーく伸ばして
Now, reach out to those horns and cheeks,
おもいっきり、楽しんじゃおうね！
and let's enjoy ourselves to the fullest!
それじゃあ、いっくよーーーっ！
Alright, let's go~!
アミーを！カケーロ！
Amii, Kakero!
ディバ！ギラファ！（uh！！）
Diba, Girafa! (Uh!)
kabu-kuwa（hey！！）
Kabu-kuwa (Hey!)
ギラギラ最高だね kabu-kuwa
Giragira is the best, kabu-kuwa!
（amore kabu-kuwa yeah！！）
(Amore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!!)
（prrrrrrr how！！）
(Prrrrrrr How!!)
kabu-kuwa（hey！！）
Kabu-kuwa (Hey!)
クリクリおめみラブ kabu-kuwa
Kurikuri omemi love, kabu-kuwa!
目覚めたなら 元気に おはよう
When you wake up, say good morning cheerfully!
（Let's Go！！ カブクワパラダイス）
(Let's Go!! Kabu-Kuwa Paradise)
お洒落なんて そっちのけ 出かけよう
Fanciness is for the other way, let's head out!
「行ってきまーーす！」
("I'm heading out!")
エレファス コーカサス ヘラクレス
Elephas, Caucasus, Heracles,
ノコギリ タランドゥス（ha！！ha！！ha！！ha！！）
Nokogiri-Talandus! (Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!)
さあ！ファンミーティングが始まる（uh wah！！）
Now, the fan meeting begins! (Uh Wah!!)
出ておいでよ
Come on out!
アミーを！カケーロ！
Amii, Kakero!
ディバ！ギラファ！（uh！！）
Diba, Girafa! (Uh!)
kabu-kuwa（hey！！）
Kabu-kuwa (Hey!)
ギラギラ最大きゅきゅ kabu-kuwa
Giragira biggest kabu-kuwa!
（amore kabu-kuwa yeah！！）
(Amore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!!)
（prrrrrrr how！！）
(Prrrrrrr How!!)
kabu-kuwa（hey！！）
Kabu-kuwa (Hey!)
テカテカツヤツヤの kabu-kuwa
Tekateka-tsuyatsuya kabu-kuwa!
（Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah！！）
(Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!!)
ぱっつん（fu！！）前髪ムッチャムッチャ（ムッチャムッチャ）
Patsun (Fu!!) Fumiama Smooth-mooth!
可愛い（fu！！）樹液をペロペロ（ペロペロ）
Kawae (Fu!!) Sap Tree Sap Lick-lick!
（awawa-wawawa！！）
(Awawa-wawawa!!)
みんな（fu！！）集まれゾロゾロ（ゾロゾロ）
Everyone (Fu!!) gather round, zoro-zoro!
こん^^chu☆（chu☆）chu☆（chu☆）
Ko-n^^chu☆ (Chu☆) chu☆ (chu☆)
パヤパヤパヤパヤ（パヤパ！）
Paya paya paya paya (Paya!)
皮付きバナナと砂糖と焼酎（焼酎）
Banana with peel, sugar, and shochu
たっぷり袋に加えたまえ（加えましょう）
Add plenty into the bag! (Add it!)
両手でクワッと鷲掴み（鷲掴み）さあ！
Squish and grab with both hands! (Grab it!)
（揉んで揉んで揉んで揉んで！）
(Knead it, knead it, knead it, knead it!)
発酵させた愛の樹液（樹液）
Fermented love sap (Sap!)
i want you 君専用ジェリー（ジェリー）
I want you, your very own jewelry!
カブクワ欲しけりゃ塗りたくれ！（塗りたくれ！）
If you want a kabu-kuwa, smear it on thick! (Smear it on!)
塗ったら 揺らせ
Smear it, shake it!
揺さ振れ！
Shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it!
落ちなきゃ 叩け
If it drops, strike it!
バンバン！ バンバンバン！
Bang-bang! Bang-bang-bang!
採れ なきゃ 踊れ
If you can't harvest it, dance!
ヘイ！ ヘイ！ ヘイ！ ヘイ！ ヘイ！ ヘイ！ ヘイ！ ヘイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
へーーーーーイ！！！
Heyyyyyyy!
すごーーい！みんなのおかげで、
Incredible! Thanks to all of you,
こんなにたくさんのかぶくわたちが集まってきてくれたよーーっ！！
so many kabu-kuwa friends have gathered!
自分に拍手〜！そして、
Give yourselves a round of applause,
自然に拍手ーーーーーっ！！
and naturally, a round of applause to everyone!
アヌビス レギウスマルマルス
Anubissh Legu's Marumaru-su
ニジイロ グランディス（ha！！ha！！ha！！ha！！）
Nijiiro Grandis (Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!)
みんなそれぞれ愛してるけど
Everyone loves each of them, but
やっぱり君が好き（誰だ？誰だ？）（誰なんだーーっ！）
you love me the most, right? (Who? Who?) (Who could it be?!)
ギラギラギラファ ギラギラギラファ
Giragira Girafa, Giragira Girafa
強くてカッコいい（え！！）
Strong and cool! (Yay!)
ギラギラ ファンタスティックなノコギリは（uh wah！！）
Giragira Fantastic Nokogiri is (Uh Wah!!)
宝物だよ
a treasure!
アミーを！カケーロ！ディバ！ギラファ！（uh！！）
Amiae! Kakero! Diba! Girafa! (Uh!)
kabu-kuwa（hey！！）
Kabu-kuwa (Hey!)
ギラギラ最高だね kabu-kuwa
Giragira is the best, kabu-kuwa!
（amore kabu-kuwa yeah！！）
(Amore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!!)
（prrrrrrr how！！）
(Prrrrrrr How!!)
kabu-kuwa（hey！！）
Kabu-kuwa (Hey!)
クリクリおめみラブ kabu-kuwa
Kurikuri amemi love, kabu-kuwa!
（Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah！！）
(Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!!)
kabu-kuwa（hey！！）
Kabu-kuwa (Hey!)
こん^^chu☆（chu☆）chu☆（chu☆）
Ko-n^^chu☆ (Chu☆) chu☆ (chu☆)
パヤパヤパヤパヤ（パヤパ！）
Paya paya paya paya (Paya!)
みんな今日は見に来てくれて、ありがとねーーっ！
Everyone who came to watch today, thank you so much~!
このあともう少し、ありだよ！
There's a little more after this, okay?
ぽっぴぽっぴぽっぴぽー！
Poppippoppippop-po-!
はっぴっぽー！
Happippo~!
さあ呑め お好きだろ 野菜ジュース
Now, do you like it? Vegetable juice!
私が決めた いま決めた
I decided, I just decided!
だから呑んで 私の 野菜ジュース
So drink up, my vegetable juice!
価格は200円！
The price is 200 yen!
まろやか 野菜ジュース
Mellow vegetable juice,
ふわふわ 野菜ジュース
fluffy fluffy vegetable juice,
いちばん おすすめなのは
the one I recommend the most
みどりのジュースゥゥー！
is green juice!
ベジタブルな あ…
Vegetable, ah...
ぽっぴっぽー ぽっぴっぽー
PoPiPo, PoPiPo
生命あふれた
Overflowing with life,
ぽっぴっぽー ぽっぴっぽー
PoPiPo, PoPiPo
あなたも今
Right now, you too—
ぽっぴっぽー ぽっぴっぽー
PoPiPo, PoPiPo
野菜ジュースが好きになる
Will come to love vegetable juice!
みんなありがとう！歌ってみた聞いてね！バイバーイ！
Thank you everyone! Check out my cover song! Bye-bye!